Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Oh no no no no
I remember it like it was yesterday
I was just running single-mindedly
And before I realized, I was standing still,
Unable to move forward
But there's a place that I want to reach,
So I'll continue walking
And I’ll be holding on to the light
That I received from you
Towards the other side
of the dream I envisioned
I’m sure I can walk together with you
We are still dreamers, dreamers
Go closer and closer, without hesitation
This feeling is getting closer (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
It’ll always be in my heart (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
Don't ever let go of this hand
We'll walk together
towards tomorrow
One step at a time
Sometimes I make mistakes
ut because you're here, today, I'll only look forward
The promise we decided on
It's a secret nobody else knows
Before I realized it
you were always by my side
As I hugged my knees and looked down
You reached out towards me
Even up till now
I can't forget the warmth of that smile
If something
Had been just a little different
Maybe we would have never met
We are still dreamers, dreamers
Little by little, together with you
The memories of the two of us that we carved (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
It's a miracle that will never happen again (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
Even if it wasn't fate
But just a coincidence
This special feeling
Will never change
Even if we get battered by the wind and rain
Even if we get tossed around by the rough waves
Even if we can't see where we're headed yet
We don't need to hide
Our weak hearts
It's alright, believe in yourself
We are still dreamers, dreamers
Go closer and closer, without hesitation
This feeling is getting closer (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
It'll always be in my heart (Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah)
Don’t ever let go of this hand
We'll walk together
Towards tomorrow
One step at a time